<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 12:57:33 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Veep - HBO</title>
      <link>/posts/veep/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 12:57:33 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/veep/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Just as a note&amp;hellip; I mention incredibly light spoilers for the end of Veep, and less light spoilers for Game of Thrones below.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just finished watching &lt;em&gt;Veep&lt;/em&gt; yesterday. I liked it a lot. The middle seasons (3-5) were probably my favorite and have a lot of the same charm that a lot of other ensemble cast shows I&amp;rsquo;ve loved (&lt;em&gt;The Office, Parks &amp;amp; Rec,&lt;/em&gt; etc.) had back in the day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now and Then - The Beatles in 2023</title>
      <link>/posts/now-and-then/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:45:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/now-and-then/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wow. Kind of an emotionally charged listen. As a long-time fan of the Beatles, I think &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/APJAQoSCwuA?si=jnNf0CDD8tPH0Us7&#34;&gt;the story behind this song&lt;/a&gt; is really touching, and to think that&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A) I’m able to say that I was alive when the Beatles released “new music” (something that is causing some cognitive dissonance), and&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;B) that this is being called their “final song,”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;just makes me feel a bit overwhelmed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Truth be told, as a song, I would mostly say it was fine. I would probably consider it a less standout track for the Beatles had it been included on any of their previous albums. That said, it&amp;rsquo;s still a Beatles song, so it still holds some merit to me, and I think there’s a tremendous amount of weight behind the song all the same.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Blog, Who Dis?</title>
      <link>/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 12:57:33 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! I&amp;rsquo;m currently moving my blog over to Hugo as opposed to write.bz. I like write.bz, and while it might be tough losing federation, I think that this is the best move for the blog moving forward. I&amp;rsquo;ll be moving all of my posts over at some point in the near term future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Productivity, ADHD and Perfectionism</title>
      <link>/posts/productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 13:50:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/productivity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just wanted to lay out a thought that’s been bouncing around my head now for a while.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I left school and confronted the pressures and responsibilities that come with adult life, I quickly realized that my previous strategy of half-assing my life quickly wasn’t effective anymore. You can’t half-ass an office job. You can’t half-ass paying your bills on time. If you want to make people feel comfortable in your home, you can’t half-ass things like taking out the trash or keeping your place clean.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threads</title>
      <link>/posts/threads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 13:47:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/threads/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This will be my only post about Threads since I don’t care to give it the time or attention it doesn’t need.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As it stands right now, it feels chaotic and impersonal. While Mastodon feels like a nice community where I follow real blogs (micro as they may be) that I’m interested in. Threads feels like the old social media dick measuring contest to see who can make the most bottom-of-the-barrel joke the fastest and subsequently rake in the most likes/reposts the fastest.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Introductory Post</title>
      <link>/posts/an-introductory-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:22:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/an-introductory-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello -&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bear with me since this is my first blog post. I’ll try to keep it short and sweet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My name is Mason. I’m a creative living in Chicago. I use the vague word “creative” here because I’m a bit of a Jack of all trades, master of none. Basically, my ideas to output ratio is very low (likely as a result of my ADHD). A lot of different mediums resonate with me, but I have trouble seeing things through. Obviously I’m learning to change that, and I even independently released my first EP of produced music a couple of months ago! It’s all a work in progress.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
